[{"answer": "I was told that he had firearms and I know of a party that he had shot at.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "And Casper, did you see him with firearms or were you aware of him having firearms?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "No, I wasn't.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Were you therefore surprised or shocked when you heard what had happened?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Well, it was pride, and you know just my heart was full.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "What was your reaction watching your good friend?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "Well, I think we have a realistic chance at getting some common sense reforms passed.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "Is there any realistic chance of, say, a renewal of the assault weapons ban?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "Well, my jurisdiction surrounds the entire city of Baltimore and as you stated the Baltimore has -- the city itself has seen significant, you know, gun violence as well as other cities across America.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "What was your takeaway from the day and the sort of level of optimism you may feel about actual action being done?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "That has to be enough, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "Well, I had to be like that way because during those times it's hard and you had a lot of games there, you know, in the area where we were living.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "How do you respond to that?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "Yeah, it is.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "Sad, isn't it?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Well you had all those kids running around hollering around and hollering, dad, dad, dad, you know, and it gets to be -- it sounds kind of funny to me.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "So come on, why wouldn't you let your daughter call you dad?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "Well, I'm glad I was tough, because look what I came out with.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "But do you have any regrets that you may have been a little bit too tough on some of them?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Well, Paris is -- even Michael said, she a piece of work, you know, because, most girls are hard to raise.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "What would you say to her afterwards?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "Oh, no.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "Are you as tough with Michael's kids, because he is not around, as you were with Michael and his siblings?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "In Blanket I do.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "Do you see Michael in them?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "I was -- I was in Las Vegas.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Where were you when you heard that Michael had died?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "Well, the saddest part about the whole thing was, Michael tried to reach me He says call my father.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "What did you do when you heard that, after you took the call?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "Yes, I did know he was doing that number of shows.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "Did you know he was doing that number of shows?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "Well, you know, that -- there was a reason why that happened.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "As his father, how did you feel when he was accused of abusing children?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "I wish he had never done that.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "Do you wish he had never done that?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, Michael was a big old kid himself.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "But did you ever worry that the perception of what he was doing wasn't good for him or his image?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "There's nothing concerning.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "You never saw anything that concerned you?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "Well, they've got motives, you know.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "Or what is it?", "qSentId": 605}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "Do you still love each other?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "ACKSON: The truth is that they had a big fight up there.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "What's the truth?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "I don't think you can get too rich too young.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "Or are you going to try and protect that, make sure they are not too rich too young?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "I'd like his legacy to be what he wanted to be.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "What would you like Michael's legacy to be?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "I've got a documentary coming out and it's a big one.", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 695, "question": "What else would you like to say?", "qSentId": 694}, {"answer": "\"Journey in My Shoes\".", "docId": "130130pmt", "aSentId": 702, "question": "And what is the thesis of the documentary?", "qSentId": 701}]